<?xml version="1.0"?>
<rss version="2.0">
   <channel>
      <title>TorChat Updates</title>
      <link>http://torchat.googlecode.com/</link>
      <description>Updates and news around the anonymous instant messenger TorChat</description>
      <language>en-us</language>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2008 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 May 2003 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
      <item>
         <title>Version 0.9.9.149 is released</title>
         <link>http://code.google.com/p/torchat/downloads/detail?name=torchat-windows-0.9.9.149.zip</link>
         <description>Version 0.9.9.149 is ready for download. Many things
         in the GUI have been improved. Incoming messages can now be opened
         in the background, the taskbar icon will flash. If a delayed (offline)
         Message is finally sent, a notification with time stamp will be created.
         All windows and the taskbar icon show now the own ID, this is useful
         if you are running more than one instance. The annoying flicker of
         the buddy list, which was introduced with .140 has also been fixed.</description>
         <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2008 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
         <guid>0.9.9.149</guid>
      </item>
      <item>
         <title>Version 0.9.9.140 is released</title>
         <link>http://code.google.com/p/torchat/downloads/detail?name=torchat-windows-0.9.9.140.zip</link>
         <description>Version 0.9.9.140 is ready for download. This release
         has some improvements in the protocol which are incompatible to older
         releases, so you all should update as soon as possible. The changes 
         have become necessary to smooth the way to some planned features like
         chat rooms and conferences and to fix some flaws in the way buddies
         were added and removed. Also new in this release are pseudo offline
         messages which are stored on the sender's machine until both, sender 
         and receiver see each other online the next time.</description>
         <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2008 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
         <guid>0.9.9.140</guid>
      </item>
      <item>
         <title>Windows binary of 0.9.9.109 now in the download area as normal</title>
         <link>http://code.google.com/p/torchat/downloads/detail?name=torchat-windows-0.9.9.109.zip</link>
         <description>My quota has now been increased by Google and the windows
         binary can now be found in the download area. Current version is
         0.9.9.109. This version has proven to be the most stable version to date.
         Several bugs have been fixed in this release and the process of
         connecting to buddies is now faster and more reliable.</description>
         <pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2008 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
         <guid>0.9.9.109-1</guid>
      </item>
      <item>
         <title>Version 0.9.9.109 is released</title>
         <link>http://code.google.com/p/torchat/downloads/detail?name=torchat-source-0.9.9.109.zip</link>
         <description>Version 0.9.9.109 is released. I have made some changes in the way and the order
         in which buddies on the list are connected. New in this version is support for a configuration file.
         You can now use an already running tor proxy in your network by specifying adress and port
         numbers (you mus also configure a hidden service on this proxy). Unfortubetely I hit the quota 
         and am still waiting for Google to increase my limit until I can upload the windows binary.</description>
         <pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2008 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
         <guid>0.9.9.109</guid>
      </item>
   </channel>
</rss>